let Hardquiz = [
    {
        question: `Every _____ years Earth and Mars are at a opposition?`,
        options: [`1.5`, `2`, `2.5`, `3`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `2`
    },
    {
        question: `How long is one Martian Year?`,
        options: [`687 Days`, `639 Days`, `712 Days`, `693 Days`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `687 Days`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the closest Star System closest to the Solar System?`,
        options: [`Barnard's Star`, `Sirius A`, `UV Ceti A`, `Proxima Centauri`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Proxima Centauri`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the oldest university in the world?`,
        options: [`University of al-Qarawinyyin`, `University of Bologna`, `University of Oxford`, `University of Salamanca`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `University of al-Qarawinyyin`
    },
    {
        question: `Who was the inventor of HTML?`,
        options: [`Tim Berners-Lee`, `Bob Kahn`, `Vint Cerf`, `Alan Turing`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Tim Berners-Lee`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the integral of 3?`,
        options: [`3`, `x`, `3x`, `None`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `3x`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the highest speed limit in the US?`,
        options: [`80mph`, `85mph`, `90mph`, `95mph`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `85mph`
    },
    {
        question: `How was the inventor of the first car?`,
        options: [`Karl Benz`, `Henry Ford`, `Enzo Ferrari`, `Ferruccio Lamborghini`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Karl Benz`
    },
    {
        question: `Ken Thompson and Dennis Ritchie co-created which operating system?`,
        options: [`Unix`, `Linux`, `Windows`, `macOS`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Unix`
    },
    {
        question: `Napoleon suffered defeat at Waterloo in what year?`,
        options: [`1815`, `1817`, `1813`, `1819`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `1815`
    },
    {
        question: `Emetophobia is the fear of?`,
        options: [`Space`, `Ocean`, `Technology`, `Vomit`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Vomit`
    },
    {
        question: `How long is a “jiffy”?`,
        options: [`1 minute`, `1 second`, `1 billionth of a second`, ` One trillionth of a second`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: ' One trillionth of a second'
    },
    {
        question: `Which poison do apple seeds contain?`,
        options: [`Cyanide`, `Sulfar`, `Botulinum`, `tetrodotoxin`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Cyanide`
    },
    {
        question: `What planet is the largest in the solar system?`,
        options: [`Jupiter`, `Saturn`, `Neptune`, `Earth`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Jupiter`
    },
    {
        question: `On the periodic table, which element has an atomic weight of 1.00794?`,
        options: [`Helium`, `Hydrogen`, `Chloride`, `Iron`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Hydrogen`
    },
    {
        question: `Which planet has moons that are nearly all named after Shakespearean characters?`,
        options: [`Jupiter`, `Neptune`, `Uranus`, `Pluto`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Uranus`
    },
    {
        question: `How many edges does a dodecahedron have`,
        options: [`22`, `26`, `30`, `40`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `30`
    },
    {
        question: `What country has competitive office chair racing?`,
        options: [`China`, `Korea`, `Japan`, `Peru`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Japan`
    },
    {
        question: `Number of vertices in a hyperdodecahedron?`,
        options: [`400`, `100`, `600`, `800`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `600`
    },
    {
        //20
        question: `Dendrophobia is the fear of what?`,
        options: [`Cars`, `Phones`, `Trees`, `Grass`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Trees`
    },
    {
        question: `How many legs does a spider have?`,
        options: [`8`, `10`, `6`, `4`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `8`
    },
    {
        question: `What is a hyperboloid?`,
        options: [`3D Parabola`, `3D Cylinder`, `3D Cone`, `3D Ellipse`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `3D Parabola`
    },
    {
        question: `What island state was formerly known by the name Formosa?`,
        options: [`Hawaii`, `Taiwan`, `Fiji`, `Cancun`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Taiwan`
    },
    {
        question: `How long do platelets live?`,
        options: [`8-12 Days`, `2-3 Weeks`, `1-2 Year`, `5-10 Minutes`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `8-12 Days`
    },
    {
        question: `Trypophobia is the fear of what?`,
        options: [`Holes`, `Mice`, `Bridges`, `Buildings`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Venus`
    },
    {   //26
        question: `What is the fear of Coulrophobia?`,
        options: [`Clowns`, `Lawyers`, `Doctors`, `Needles`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Clowns`
    },
    {
        question: `The universe is roughy ____ years old?`,
        options: [`14 Billion`, `12 Billion`, `6 Billion`, `24 Billion`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `14 Billion`
    },
    {
        question: `Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious is another meaning for?`,
        options: [`Wonderful`, `Sadly`, `Excited`, `Ghastly`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Wonderful`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the oldest bacteria called?`,
        options: [`Cyanobacteria `, `Rhodospirillales`, `Spirillum`, `Clostridium tetani`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Cyanobacteria `
    },
    {
        //30
        question: `How Many Earths Could Fit Inside The Sun?`,
        options: [`1 Million`, `1.3 Million`, `1.5 Million`, `Alot`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `1.3 Million`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the name of the number of 10 to the power of googol?`,
        options: [`googol`, `googolplex`, `plexgooglo`, `quattuordecillion`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `googolplex`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the distance between Earth and the center of the Milky Way galaxy?`,
        options: [`10000 Light Years`, `250000 Light Years`, `25000 Light Years`, `15000 Light Years`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `25000 Light Years`
    },
    {
        question: `Which year was the first exoplanet discovered in?`,
        options: [`1998`, `1898`, `1995`, `1895`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `1995`
    },
    {
        question: `What type of galaxy is the most common in the universe?`,
        options: [`Elliptical`, `Spiral`, `Irregular`, `Nebula`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Elliptical`
    },
    {
        question: `How cold is The Boomerang Nebula?`,
        options: [`-458F`, `-578F`, `-398F`, `-621F`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `-458F`
    },
    {
        question: `What has an incredibly strong gravitational pull that light can’t even escape?`,
        options: [`Black Hole`, `Nebula`, `Galaxy`, `Event Horizon`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Black Hole`
    },
    {
        //37
        question: `What was the world first computer bug?`,
        options: [`Moth`, `Binary`, `Hexadecimal`, `Unicode`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Moth`
    },
    {
        question: `It is said Chernobyl nuclear power plant will remain uninhabitable until`,
        options: [`22000`, `20000`, `21000`, `23000`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `22000`
    },
    {
        question: `Earth atmosphere contain ____% of Nitrogen?`,
        options: [`28`, `33`, `50`, `78`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `78`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the most popular anime of all time?`,
        options: [`Dragon Ball`, `One Piece`, `Naruto`, `Pokemon`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Dragon Ball`
    },
    {
        question: `when was github founded?`,
        options: [`2008`, `2009`, `2005`, `2006`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `2008`
    },
    {
        question: `What did nintendo first sell?`,
        options: [`Cards`, `Games`, `Figures`, `Paper`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Cards`
    },
    {
        //43
        question: `What is the 100th digit of Pi?`,
        options: [`4`, `9`, `7`, `1`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `9`
    },
    {
        question: `What is isobutylphenylpropanoic acid more commonly known as?`,
        options: [`Ibuprofen`,`Morphine`,`Ketamine`,`Aspirin`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Ibuprofen`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the unit of currency in Laos?`,
        options: [`Kip`, `Ruble`, `Konra`, `Dollar`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Kip`
    },
    {
        question: `In what year did the Wall Street Crash take place?`,
        options: [`1929`, `1930`, `1932`, `1925`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `1929`
    },
    {
        question: `How many manned moon landings have there been??`,
        options: [`6`, `4`, `2`, `1`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `6`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the scientific name of the knee cap?`,
        options: [`Patella`, `Femur`, `Scapula`, `Foramen Magnum`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Patella`
    },
    {
        question: `Botanically speaking, which of these fruits is NOT a berry?`,
        options: [`Banana`, `Blueberry`, `Concord Grape`, `Strawberry`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Strawberry`
    },
    {
        question: `What is the oldest Disney film?`,
        options: [`Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs`, `Dumbo`, `Fantasia`, `Pinocchio`].sort(() => Math.random() - .50),
        answer: `Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs`
    },
].sort(() => Math.random() - .50).slice(0,20);

export default Hardquiz;